Miscellany
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Miscellany
2.1.2.11.2
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1444
- Miscellany, 2.1.2.11.2
  - World Fliers’ symbol, 1924; 9; 3x4 color (Box 1444)
  - World Fliers’ symbol, 1924; 10; 3x4 b&w (Box 1444)
  - The young lady whose picture on celluloid flew round the world on the instrument board of the New Orleans, 1924; 11; 3x4 color (Box 1444)
  - Lowell Thomas and World Fliers in front of plane, 1924; 12; 3x4 b&w (Box 1444)
  - World Fliers posing with globe, 1924; 13; 3x4 b&w (Box 1444)
  - World Fliers posing for photograph, 1924; 14; 3x4 b&w (Box 1444)
  - World Flier in uniform posing for photograph, 1924; 15; 3x4 color (Box 1444)
  - Two World Fliers posing for photograph, 1924; 16; 3x4 color (Box 1444)
  - Two World Fliers posing for photograph, 1924; 17; 3x4 b&w (Box 1444)
  - World Fliers in front of plane, one holding a raccoon, 1924; 18; 3x4 b&w (Box 1444)
  - New Orleans airplane being examined, 1924; 19; 3x4 color (Box 1444)
  - Men working on seaplane onboard ship, 1924; 20; 3x4 color (Box 1444)
  - Two airplanes flying over clouds, photograph taken from above, 1924; 21; 3x4 color (Box 1444)
  - Two airplanes flying through clouds, photograph taken from airplane, 1924; 22; 3x4 color (Box 1444)
  - Two airplanes flying over clouds, photograph taken from airplane, 1924; 23; 3x4 b&w (Box 1444)
  - Airplane flying over clouds, photograph taken from other airplane, 1924; 24; 3x4 color (Box 1444)
  - Many airplanes flying over city, 1924; 25; 3x4 b&w (Box 1444)
  - Airplane flying over city, photograph taken from other airplane, 1924; 26; 3x4 b&w (Box 1444)
  - Airplane flying over city, photograph taken from other airplane, 1924; 27; 3x4 b&w (Box 1444)
  - Airplane flying low over city, 1924; 28; 3x4 b&w (Box 1444)
  - View of unidentified city, 1924; 29; 3x4 b&w (Box 1444)
  - View of river and city from airplane (aerial view), 1924; 30; 3x4 b&w (Box 1444)
  - Three airplanes flying over city, 1924; 31; 3x4 color (Box 1444)
  - Three airplanes flying over city, 1924; 32; 3x4 color (Box 1444)
  - Airplane flying in front of mountains, photograph taken from airplane, 1924; 33; 3x4 color (Box 1444)
  - Airplane flying over mountains, photograph taken from airplane, 1924; 34; 3x4 color (Box 1444)
  - Airplane flying over mountains, photograph taken from airplane, 1924; 35; 3x4 b&w (Box 1444)
  - Two airplanes flying over mountains, photograph taken from airplane, 1924; 36; 3x4 color (Box 1444)
  Box 1445
- Miscellany, 2.1.2.11.2
  - Airplane flying over mountain, 1924; 1; 3x4 color (Box 1445)
  - Airplane flying over mountain, 1924; 2; 3x4 b&w (Box 1445)
  - Two airplanes flying over mountain, 1924; 3; 3x4 color (Box 1445)
  - View of mountains from airplane, 1924; 4; 3x4 color (Box 1445)
  - Airplane flying over water, mountains in distance, photograph taken from airplane, 1924; 5; 3x4 b&w (Box 1445)
  - Two airplanes flying over water, mountains in distance, 1924; 6; 3x4 b&w (Box 1445)
  - Airplane flying over fields, photograph taken from airplane, 1924; 7; 3x4 b&w (Box 1445)
  - Airplane flying over fields, photograph taken from airplane, 1924; 8; 3x4 b&w (Box 1445)
  - Two seaplanes on water, 1924; 9; 3x4 b&w (Box 1445)
  - Airplanes flying over river and fields, 1924; 10; 3x4 color (Box 1445)
  - Seaplane flying over river and forest, 1924; 11; 3x4 color (Box 1445)
  - Three seaplanes flying over palm trees, 1924; 12; 3x4 color (Box 1445)
  - Seaplane flying above three boats, 1924; 13; 3x4 color (Box 1445)
  - Seaplane flying over water, 1924; 14; 3x4 b&w (Box 1445)
  - Seaplane landing on water, photograph taken from airplane, 1924; 15; 3x4 b&w (Box 1445)
  - Seaplane on water, 1924; 16; 3x4 b&w (Box 1445)
  - Seaplanes on water, mountains in distance, 1924; 17; 3x4 b&w (Box 1445)
  - Seaplanes on water, mountains in distance, 1924; 18; 3x4 b&w (Box 1445)
  - Lake in midst of mountains, 1924; 19; 3x4 b&w (Box 1445)
  - Mountain, 1924; 20; 3x4 b&w (Box 1445)
  - View of water and land from airplane (aerial view), 1924; 21; 3x4 b&w (Box 1445)
  - View of river from airplane (aerial view), 1924; 22; 3x4 b&w (Box 1445)
  - Looking down at the flagship of the scuttled German fleet at Scapa Flow, 1924; 23; 3x4 b&w (Box 1445)
  - Boats on coast, 1924; 24; 3x4 b&w (Box 1445)